A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.3-SG 1.8 (A76-A82) FA209
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects (A78), 1873-1997; 5; 56.56 Cubic Feet 151 containers.; Document boxes 237-382.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.08 Cubic Feet 16 letter document boxes
    - Scholars - Schreiber, E., 1972-1975 (Box 248, Folder 1540, Folder 1549)
    - Scholars - Siegel, B., 1972-1975 (Box 248, Folder 1541)
    - Scholars - Sorensen, T. (did not go), 1974 (Box 248, Folder 1542)
    - Scholars - Stansky, P., 1972-1974, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 1543)
    - Scholars - Stebbins, G.L., 1972-1974 (Box 248, Folder 1544)
    - Scholars - Stein, E, 1972-1974, 1977 (Box 248, Folder 1545)
    - Scholars - Stern and Landes, 1971-1972, 1977 (Box 248, Folder 1546)
    - Scholars - Stevens, C.H., 1972-1974 (Box 248, Folder 1547)
    - Scholars - Stevens, D., 1972-1973, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 1548)
    - Scholars - Stolper, W, 1972-1975 (Box 248, Folder 1549)
    - Scholars - Storry, R, 1973-1974, 1980 (Box 248, Folder 1550)
    - Scholars - Sussna, F, 1970-1974 (Box 249, Folder 1551)
    - Scholars - Talmon, J, 1973 (Box 249, Folder 1552)
    - Scholars - Touraine, A, 1973-1974 (Box 249, Folder 1553)
    - Scholars - Tuchman, B (did not go), 1973 (Box 249, Folder 1554)
    - Scholars - Vaizey, J., 1972-1974 (Box 249, Folder 1555)
    - Scholars - Valentino, J., 1973-1974 (Box 249, Folder 1556)
    - Scholars - Von Geusau, F., 1972-1973, 1976 (Box 249, Folder 1557-1558)
    - Scholars - Waddington, C.H., 1974-1975 (Box 249, Folder 1559)
    - Scholars - Ward, R.E., 1971-1973 (Box 249, Folder 1560)
    - Scholars - Warren, K.S., 1972-1983 (Box 249, Folder 1561)
    - Scholars - Wharton, C., 1972-1973 (Box 249, Folder 1562)
    - Scholars - Wheeler, J., 1972-1974 (Box 249, Folder 1563)
    - Scholars - Wood, B., 1972-1973 (Box 249, Folder 1564)
    - Scholars - Yost, C.W. (Box 250, Folder 1565)
    - Scholars - Young, L. (Box 250, Folder 1566)
    - Social Science Research Conference, 1973 (Box 250, Folder 1567)
    - Social Science Research Conference, 1974 (Box 250, Folder 1568)
    - Social Science Research Conference - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974 (Box 250, Folder 1569-1571)
    - Social Science Research Council - Western European Fellowships Conference, 1973-1975 (Box 251, Folder 1572)
    - Technology Diffusion Conference, 1970-1973 (Box 251, Folder 1573)
    - Transatlantic Cooperation - Conference, 1972-1974 (Box 251, Folder 1574)
    - Tropical Medicine - Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 251, Folder 1575-1576)
    - United States - European Relations - Conference, 1973-1976 (Box 251, Folder 1577)
    - University of Bergen - Politics Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 251, Folder 1578)
    - University of the Future - Conference, 1970-1972 (Box 252, Folder 1579)
    - University of Michigan - Economics Planning Conference, 1972-1976 (Box 252, Folder 1580)
    - University of South Carolina - East European Social Science Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 252, Folder 1582)
    - Yale University - Agriculture Conference, 1971-1973, 1975 (Box 252, Folder 1583)
    - 152 - Unemployment and Human Utilization Conference, 1971 (Box 252, Folder 1584)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150; 3.04 Cubic Feet 8 letter document boxes
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Hawaii, 214
      - University of Hawaii - Renaud (Box 252, Folder 1585)
      - University of Hawaii - Renaud, 1972-1977 (Box 252, Folder 1585)
      - University of Hawaii - Renaud - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974 (Box 253, Folder 1586)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Illinois, 216
      - University of Illinois - Choldin, 1973-1976 (Box 253, Folder 1587-1589)
      - University of Illinois - Choldin - Supplementary Material, 1973-1975, 1978 (Box 253, Folder 1590, Box 254, Folder 1591)
      - University of Illinois - Flanagan, 1972-1978 (Box 254, Folder 1592-1593)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Massachusetts, 224
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Cornelius, 1972-1977 (Box 254, Folder 1594)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Cornelius - Supplementary Materials, 1973-1974 (Box 254, Folder 1595, Box 255, Folder 1596-1597, Box 256, Folder 1598)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Michigan, 225
      - Western Michigan University - Keely, 1973-1977 (Box 256, Folder 1599)
      - Western Michigan University - Keely - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 256, Folder 1600)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - New York, 235
      - Columbia University - Farley, 1972-1977 (Box 257, Folder 1601)
      - State University of New York - Naroll, 1973-1981 (Box 257, Folder 1602-1605)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Pennsylvania, 241
      - Pennsylvania State University - McIntyre, 1973-1979 (Box 258, Folder 1606)
      - Pennsylvania State University - McIntyre - Supplementary Material, 1973-1975 (Box 258, Folder 1607)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Pack, 1974-1977 (Box 258, Folder 1608-1609)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Pack - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 258, Folder 1610-1611)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Wisconsin, 255
      - University of Wisconsin - Lindert, 1972-1977 (Box 259, Folder 1612-1614)
      - University of Wisconsin - Lindert - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974 (Box 259, Folder 1615-1618)
  - Unemployment and Human Resource Utilization, 152; 1.7 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes
    - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
      - Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 260, Folder 1619)
      - Conference, 1972-1976 (Box 260, Folder 1620)
      - Conference - Supplementary Material, 1970 (Box 260, Folder 1621)
      - Conference - Invitees - A-Z, 1970-1971 (Box 260, Folder 1622-1623)
    - United States, 200
      - East-West Technology and Development Institute Adaptive Technology, 1972, 1976 (Box 260, Folder 1624)
      - East-West Technology and Development Institute Adaptive Technology, 1972-1973 (Box 261, Folder 1625)
    - Brazil, 305
      - Northeast Brazil - Human Resources, 1972-1977 (Box 261, Folder 1626-1628)
      - Northeast Brazil - Human Resources - Supplementary Material, 1974-1977 (Box 261, Folder 1629-1630)
    - Venezuela, 339
      - Center of Social Studies - Women and Work, 1971-1975 (Box 262, Folder 1631-1632)
      - Center of Social Studies - Women and Work - Supplementary Material, 1970-1975 (Box 262, Folder 1633-1636, Box 263, Folder 1637)
    - Nigeria, 497
      - University of Lagos - Human Resources, 1971-1978 (Box 263, Folder 1638)
      - University of Lagos - Human Resources - Supplementary Material, 1972, 1974-1975, 1977 (Box 263, Folder 1639-1642)
  - Conflict in International Relations, 155; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
    - American Universities Field Staff - Cyprus Conference, 1973-1976 (Box 264, Folder 1643)
    - Aspen Institute - Jerusalem Future I & II, 1974-1977 (Box 264, Folder 1644)
    - Berenyi, John, 1973-1976 (Box 264, Folder 1645)
    - Brookings Institution - Monetary Rates Conference, 1974-1976, 1981 (Box 264, Folder 1646)
    - Middle East Institute, 1973-1975 (Box 264, Folder 1647)
    - Middle East Institute - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 264, Folder 1648)
    - University of Colorado - Conflict Resolution, 1973-1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 265, Folder 1649)
    - University of Oregon - Mexican Border Industrialization, 1973-1974 (Box 265, Folder 1650)
    - Weather and Conflict Conference, 1970-1978 (Box 265, Folder 1651-1653, Box 266, Folder 1654-1655)
    - Conflict in International Relations - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - American Arbitration Association - Straus, 1973-1975 (Box 266, Folder 1656)
      - American Arbitration Association - Staus - Evaluation, 1975, 1977, 1979 (Box 266, Folder 1657)
      - American Arbitration Association - Straus - Supplementary Material, 1972-1973 (Box 266, Folder 1658)
      - American Arbitration Association - Straus - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 266, Folder 1659)
      - American Arbitration Association - Straus - Supplementary Material, 1975 Jan.-Nov. (Box 267, Folder 1660)
      - Harvard University - Lee, 1973-1976 (Box 267, Folder 1661)
      - Harvard University - Lee - Evaluation, 1977, 1979 (Box 267, Folder 1662)
      - Harvard University - Lee - Supplementary Material, 1971-1973 (Box 267, Folder 1663)
      - Harvard University - Nye, 1973-1974, 1979 (Box 267, Folder 1664)
      - Hirsch, Seev, 1973-1978 (Box 267, Folder 1665)
      - Lewis, William, 1973-1974 (Box 267, Folder 1666)
  - Education and Development in the Less-Developed Countries, 160; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
    - 160: District of Columbia, 210
      - Brookings Institution - Latin American Economic Integration, 1973-1981 (Box 267, Folder 1667)
      - Brookings Institution - Latin American Economic Integration - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 268, Folder 1668)
  - 170, 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - 170: Pennsylvania, 241
      - University of Pennsylvania - Wolf, 1971-1975 (Box 268, Folder 1669)
    - 170: Texas, 249
      - University of Texas - Kramen, 1971-1975 (Box 268, Folder 1670)
  - Drug Abuse Program, 180; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
    - Drug Abuse Program - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
      - Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 268, Folder 1671-1673)
  - United States, 200; 35.08 Cubic Feet 95 containers
    - Academy of Natural Sciences - Fresh Water Ecology, 1967-1975 (Box 269, Folder 1674-1675)
    - Academy of Natural Sciences - Fresh Water Ecology - Supplementary Material, 1949-1975 (Box 269, Folder 1676-1678)
    - Admin. and Management Research Association - Environmental Assessment, 1973-1975 (Box 270, Folder 1679)
    - American Assembly - Foundations Program, 1972-1973 (Box 270, Folder 1680-1681)
    - American Bar Foundation - Tax Reform Act, 1971-1974 (Box 270, Folder 1682-1683)
    - American Freedom from Hunger Foundation - Leadership Training, 193-1977 (Box 270, Folder 1684)
    - Americans for Indian Opportunity, 1970-1976 (Box 271, Folder 1685-1687)
    - Americans for Indian Opportunity - Supplementary Material, 1969-1970 (Box 271, Folder 1688)
    - Antioch College - Student Assistance, 1963-1975 (Box 271, Folder 1689, Box 272, Folder 1690-1691)
    - Arctic Institute of North America - Conflict Mediation, 1973-1974 (Box 272, Folder 1692)
    - Arctic Institute of North America - Conflict Mediation, 1974-1975 (Box 272, Folder 1693)
    - Arizona State University - Pre-Schoolers Parents Education, 1971-1973 (Box 272, Folder 1694)
    - Arizona State University - Pre-Schoolers Parents Education, 1973-1975 (Box 272, Folder 1695)
    - Aspire, Inc. - Guidance, 1970-1974 (Box 273, Folder 1696-1697)
    - Aspire, Inc. - Guidance - Supplementary Material, 1966-1970 (Box 272, Folder 1698)
    - Bank Street College of Education - City Schools, 1965-1975 (Box 273, Folder 1699-1702)
    - Bank Street College of Education - City Schools - Supplementary Material, 1959-1969 (Box 274, Folder 1703-1708)
    - Boston University - Language Acquisition Research Curriculum, 1970-1973 (Box 275, Folder 1709)
    - Boston University - Language Acquisition Research Curriculum - Supplementary Material, 1970-1972 (Box 275, Folder 1710-1711)
    - Brookhaven National Lab. - Metal Hybrid Systems, 1970, 1973-1975 (Box 275, Folder 1712-1713)
    - Brookhaven National Lab. - Metal Hybrid Systems - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1972-1974 (Box 275, Folder 1714)
    - California State College, Los Angeles - Locke High School, 1967-1975 (Box 276, Folder 1715-1717, Box 277, Folder 1718-1722)
    - California State College, Los Angeles - Locke High School - Supplementary Material, 1969 (Box 277, Folder 1723)
    - California State College, Los Angeles - Locke High School - Supplementary Material, 1969-1970 (Box 278, Folder 1724)
    - Center for Community Change - Education Division, 1971-1975 (Box 278, Folder 1725-1727)
    - Center for Policy Research, Inc. - Land Developers Study, 1973-1976 (Box 278, Folder 1728-1729)
    - Clark College - Burgess, 1973-1977 (Box 279, Folder 1730)
    - Clark College - Burgess - Supplementary Material, 1969-1974 (Box 279, Folder 1731-1733)
    - Community Renewal Society - Leadership Training, 1968-1976 (Box 279, Folder 1734, Box 280, Folder 1735-1739)
    - Community Renewal Society - Leadership Training - Supplementary Material, 1967-1972, 1974 (Box 281, Folder 1740-1743)
    - Cornell University - Adolescent Drug Dependency, 1970-1973 (Box 281, Folder 1744)
    - Cornell University - Adolescent Drug Dependency, 1973-1977 (Box 282, Folder 1745)
    - Cornell University - Adolescent Drug Dependency - Supplementary Material, 1970-1973 (Box 282, Folder 1746)
    - Cornell University - Student Assistance, 1967-1972 (Box 282, Folder 1747)
    - Council on Foundations, Inc. - Management Internship, 1973-1975 (Box 282, Folder 1748)
    - Del Paso Heights - Education Management Training, 1972-1974 (Box 282, Folder 1749)
    - Econ. Develop. Council - City Schools, 1971-1977 (Box 282, Folder 1750-1751, Box 283, Folder 1752-1753)
    - Econ. Develop. Council - City Schools - Supplementary Material, 1970-1973 (Box 283, Folder 1754-1756)
    - Environmental Planning & Information Center - Land Use Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 284, Folder 1757)
    - Fisk University - Development Program, 1963-1972 (Box 284, Folder 1758-1762, Box 285, Folder 1763-1765, Box 286, Folder 1766-1768)
    - Fisk University - Development Program - Supplementary Material, 1947, 1949, 1963, 1964, 1968 (Box 287, Folder 1769-1771)
    - Fisk University - Development Program - Sociology, 1966-1975 (Box 287, Folder 1772-1773)
    - Harvard University - Richardson, 1973-1976 (Box 287, Folder 1774)
    - Howard University - School Administrators Training, 1973-1977 (Box 287, Folder 1775)
    - Howard University - Technical Assistance, 1973-1977 (Box 288, Folder 1776-1777)
    - Howard University - Technical Assistance - Supplementary Material, 1964 (Box 288, Folder 1778, Folder 1779)
    - Institute for Development of Educational Activities - Overseas Schools, 1973-1974 (Box 288, Folder 1780)
    - Institute for the Future, 1973-1975 (Box 288, Folder 1781-1782)
    - Institute for the Future - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 289, Folder 1783-1785)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Chemical Pollutants, 1972-1975 (Box 289, Folder 1786-1787)
    - Medical College of Wisconsin - Insect Effect on Corn, 1973-1975 (Box 289, Folder 1788)
    - Meridian House International - Women's Year, 1974-1975 (Box 289, Folder 1789-1790)
    - Meridian House International - Women's Year - Supplementary Material, 1973-1975 (Box 289, Folder 1791)
    - Meridian House International - Women's Year - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 290, Folder 1792)
    - Merrill-Palmer Institute - Social Change and Urban Family, 1971-1974 (Box 290, Folder 1793)
    - Merrill-Palmer Institute - Social Change and Urban Family - Supplementary Material, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 290, Folder 1794)
    - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs - Africa Credentials Evaluation, 1973-1974 (Box 290, Folder 1795)
    - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs - Visa Study, 1972-1976 (Box 290, Folder 1796)
    - National Urban League - Citizenship Education, 1972-1975 (Box 290, Folder 1797-1798)
    - National Urban League - Citizenship Education - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 291, Folder 1799)
    - New Orleans - Education - Leadership Development Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 291, Folder 1800)
    - Oberlin College - Student Assistance, 1963-1973 (Box 291, Folder 1801-1803)
    - P.A.C.E. - New England Field Service Program, 1973-1975 (Box 291, Folder 1804-1805)
    - P.A.C.E. - New England Field Service Program - Supplementary Material, 1972-1973 (Box 292, Folder 1809, Folder 1807-1808)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Remedial Agric. Education, 1970-1975 (Box 292, Folder 1810)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Latin American Program, 1963-1975 (Box 293, Folder 1811-1817)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Latin American Program - Supplementary Material, 1961-1964, 1968 (Box 294, Folder 1818-1821)
    - Ravenwood - Education - Training Program, 1973-1975, 1978 (Box 294, Folder 1822-1823)
    - Resources for the Future - Environmental Quality, 1969-1975 (Box 294, Folder 1824, Box 295, Folder 1825-1827)
    - Resources for the Future - Environmental Quality - Supplementary Material, 1969, 1971-1974 (Box 295, Folder 1828-1829)
    - Revitalization Corps, 1971-1978 (Box 295, Folder 1830, Box 296, Folder 1831-1832)
    - Revitalization Corps - Supplementary Material, 1971-1978 (Box 296, Folder 1833)
    - Rocky Mountain Center on Environment - Environmental International Program, 1972-1975 (Box 296, Folder 1834-1835)
    - Rocky Mountain Center on Environment - Environmental International Program - Supplementary Material, 1971-1975 (Box 296, Folder 1836-1837)
    - Rutgers University - Donaldson, 1973-1975 (Box 296, Folder 1838-1839)
    - Rutgers University - Hudson Basin Study, 1973-1975 (Box 297, Folder 1840)
    - Rutgers University - Donaldson - Supplementary Material, 1974 March (Box 297, Folder 1841)
    - St. Olaf College - American Indian Program, 1971-1973 (Box 297, Folder 1842)
    - San Diego - Education, 1969-1974 (Box 297, Folder 1843-1846, Box 298, Folder 1847-1849)
    - Sequatchie Valley Agency - Chicken Production, 1973-1974 (Box 298, Folder 1850)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - African Studies, 1972-1975, 1981 (Box 298, Folder 1851)
    - Stanford University - Food Research Institute - African Studies - Supplementary Material, 1977 (Box 299, Folder 1854, Folder 1853, Box 298, Folder 1852)
    - SUNY at Binghamton - Environmental Analysis, 1971-1977 (Box 299, Folder 1855-1857)
    - SUNY at Binghamton - Environmental Analysis - Supplementary Material, 1970-1972 (Box 299, Folder 1858)
    - Tulane University - Leadership Development, 1972-1975 (Box 300, Folder 1859)
    - University of Alaska - Alaskan Science Conference, 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 300, Folder 1860)
    - University of Alaska - Alaskan Science Conference - Supplementary Material, 1973-1974 (Box 300, Folder 1861-1862)
    - University of California - Mexican American Students, 1967-1973 (Box 300, Folder 1863)
    - University of North Carolina - Election Study, 1972-1974 (Box 300, Folder 1864)
    - University of Southern California - Resource Sharing, 1971-1975 (Box 300, Folder 1865)
    - University of Utah - Graduate Assistance in Energy Assessment, 1973 (Box 301, Folder 1866)
    - University of Utah - Graduate Assistance in Energy Assessment - Supplementary Material, 1974 Aug. (Box 301, Folder 1867)
    - Utah State University - Environment, 1969-1974 (Box 301, Folder 1868-1872, Box 302, Folder 1873-1875)
    - Utah State University - Environment - Supplementary Material, 1970-1974 (Box 302, Folder 1876-1878, Box 303, Folder 1879-1882, Box 304, Folder 1883-1884)
    - Washington University - Work-Study Program, 1966-1974 (Box 304, Folder 1885-1888)
    - Western Washington State College - Remedial Education, 1965-1973, 1977 (Box 305, Folder 1889-1893)
    - Williams College - Environmental Studies, 1967-1974, 1976 (Box 306, Folder 1894-1898)
    - Williams College - Environmental Studies - Supplementary Material, 1968-1973 (Box 307, Folder 1899-1904, Box 308, Folder 1905-1906)
    - Wilmington - Education - Leadership Training, 1972-1973, 1978 (Box 308, Folder 1907)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute - Marine Resource Exploitation, 1972-1975 (Box 308, Folder 1908-1909)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute - Marine Resource Exploitation - Evaluation, 1975 (Box 308, Folder 1910)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute - Marine Resource Exploitation - Supplementary Material, 1972-1973 (Box 308, Folder 1911)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Barnard College - Research Ethics, 1972-1975 (Box 309, Folder 1912)
      - Cornell University - Latin American Population, 1969-1976 (Box 309, Folder 1913-1914)
      - Duke University - Health Services, 1969-1973, 1977 (Box 309, Folder 1915)
      - Duke University - Health Services - Supplementary Material, 1969-1970 (Box 309, Folder 1916)
      - Harvard University - Community Health, 1967-1977 (Box 309, Folder 1917-1918, Box 310, Folder 1919)
      - Harvard University - Community Health - Supplementary Material, 1970-1975 (Box 310, Folder 1920-1925)
      - Harvard University - Population Studies, 1963-1974 (Box 311, Folder 1926-1929)
      - Harvard University - Population Studies - Supplementary Material, 1965-1974 (Box 311, Folder 1930-1932)
      - Harvard University - Reproductive Biology Laboratory, 1972-1975 (Box 312, Folder 1933)
      - Harvard University - Surgical Care Studies, 1971-1977 (Box 312, Folder 1934-1936)
      - Harvard University - Surgical Care Studies - Books, 1975-1976 (Box 313, Folder 1937-1938, Box 314, Folder 1939-1940)
      - Harvard University - Surgical Care Studies - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 315, Folder 1941-1943, Box 316, Folder 1944)
      - Indiana University Foundation - Small Intestine Research, 1972-1975 (Box 316, Folder 1945)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Reproductive Biology Equipment, 1973-1976 (Box 316, Folder 1946)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Reproductive Biology Equipment - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 316, Folder 1947)
      - New England Hospital - Health Careers Training, 1968-1977 (Box 316, Folder 1948, Box 317, Folder 1949-1952)
      - New York University - Telemedicine, 1972-1975 (Box 317, Folder 1953, Box 318, Folder 1954-1956)
      - New York University - Telemedicine - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 318, Folder 1957-1959)
      - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Nurses Training, 1971-1972 (Box 319, Folder 1963)
      - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Nurses Training, 1972-1975 (Box 319, Folder 1964)
      - Planned Parenthood of New York City - Training Center, 1968-1976 (Box 320, Folder 1965-1967)
      - Population Crisis Commission - Population Problems Publication, 1972-1974 (Box 320, Folder 1968)
      - Population Crisis Commission - Population Problems Publication - Supplementary Material, 1972-1974 (Box 320, Folder 1969)
      - Population Crisis Commission - Population Problems Publication (Box 320, Folder 1968)
      - Stanford University - Health care Management, 1971-1974 (Box 320, Folder 1970)
      - University of Michigan - Medical Center - Willson, 1973-1974 (Box 321, Folder 1971-1972)
      - Watts Labor Community Action Committee - Paramedical Training, 1968-1975 (Box 321, Folder 1974-1977, Box 322, Folder 1978-1980)
      - Watts Labor Community Action Committee - Paramedical Training - Supplementary Material, 1970-1971 (Box 322, Folder 1981)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Agribusiness Council, Inc. - Conference, 1972-1975 (Box 322, Folder 1982-1983, Box 323, Folder 1984)
      - Agribusiness Council, Inc. - Conference - Supplementary Material, 1974 (Box 323, Folder 1985-1986)
      - Associates of the National Agricultural Library, Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 323, Folder 1987)
      - Harvard University - Maize Symposium, 1972-1975 (Box 323, Folder 1988)
      - International Center, Hawaii - East West Food Institute - Fisheries Evaluation, 1972-1976 (Box 323, Folder 1989)
      - Louisiana State University - Cellulose Waste (Declination), 1971-1974 (Box 324, Folder 1990-1993)
      - Louisiana State University - Cellulose Waste (Declination) - Supplementary Material, 1967-1972 (Box 324, Folder 1994-1995, Box 325, Folder 1996-1999)